(Amy(tablet ringing):)How's it going, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Actually, much better.
(Stuart:)Oh, good.
Is the baby born yet?
(Sheldon:)I don't know
I just got back.
(Amy:)Where'd you go?
(Sheldon:)My mother asked me
to get some towels.
(Sheldon:)I took advantage
of the vague request
(Sheldon:)and went to Bed, Bath & Beyond.
Excuse me! I'm on the phone!
(Sheldon:)So rude.
(Amy:)Here's another one.
Penny, if it weren't for Sheldon,
(Amy:)you never would have met
comic book legend Stan Lee.
(Penny:)Great.
(Raj:)At least Leonard, Howard and I
would have always been friends.
(Bernadette:)Hey, how come you three never
got an apartment together?
(Leonard:)We talked about it,
but Howard was in
(Leonard:)a pretty serious
relationship with his mom.
(Howard:)I lived with her to save money.